zoomonga.com 2010-06-24

# Zoomonga

Privacy Policy

This privacy policy pertains to the use of the Zoomonga web site at http://www.zoomonga.com 

Zoomonga, and its parent company, Listopica, Inc., respects your right to personal privacy, and we are committed to protecting that right. Therefore, we provide this Privacy Policy notice to explain our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. 

Children under 13 are not permitted to use the Zoomonga service, and so this privacy policy makes no provision for children's use of the site. 

Information is gathered from members and guests who apply for the various services our site offers. This information includes, but is not limited to: email address, first name, last name, and certain optional information such as , birth date, birth place, gender, biographical information, MSN,YAHOO, AIM, GOOGLE, ICQ user name, and personal interests. We will also ask for your billing address, phone number, and credit card information when you subscribe for a premium paid services. 

In some cases, we may use third party vendors to process your transactions on Zoomonga. For example, credit card transactions are handled by a third-party financial institution, which receives the credit card number and other personally identifying information in order to validate the purchase. 

Zoomonga automatically collects IP addresses and traffic information from visitors to our site. This information is aggregated into statistics to help us evaluate how visitors prefer to use and navigate our website, and to help us improve your experience on Zoomonga. We may share this aggregate traffic information with our partners or advertisers, but in no event, will we disclose any information that will identify you personally. Likewise, we may share aggregate sales information with third parties, but such information will not identify individual customers. 

Cookies are small text files that a website can place on a userâ€™s computer hard drive to be a unique identifier for that user. Zoomonga uses its own cookies for a number of purposes, including to access your information when you "sign in", Keep track of preferences you specify while you are using Zoomongaâ€™s services, Conduct research to improve Zoomonga,s content and services. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information while on our site. Once the user closes their browser, the cookie simply terminates. For instance, by setting a cookie on our site, the user would not have to log in a password more than once, thereby saving time while on our site. 

You can configure your browser to accept all cookies, reject all cookies, or notify you when a cookie is set. If you reject all cookies, you will not be able to use Zoomonga services that require you to "sign in," and you may not be able to take full advantage of the Zoomonga service. 

However, our site does contain links to third-party websites, that show advertisements on some of our pages set and access their cookies on your computer. Please refer to the third partyâ€™s privacy policy for details on their use of cookies. 

You can configure your browser to accept all cookies, reject all cookies, or notify you when a cookie is set. If you reject all cookies, you will not be able to use Zoomonga services that require you to "sign in," and you may not be able to take full advantage of the Zoomonga service. 

While we attempt to keep your personal information confidential, it is necessary to disclose this information to the public in some circumstances. For example, When you post a message, your Zoomonga ID or alias that you are posting under is visible to other users. If you post personal information online that is accessible to the public, you may receive unsolicited messages from other parties in return. 

Finally, we may disclose and use personally identifiable information in special circumstances when we believe, in good faith, that such release is reasonably necessary to (i) comply with law or court order, (ii) enforce or apply the terms of any of our user agreements, or (iii) protect the rights, property, or safety of Zoomonga, our users, or others. 

Furthermore, we will not share your e-mail address with third parties, unless you elect to have this information shared as part of transacting business on our site. We may use your e-mail address to send you an e-mail announcement from time to time regarding some change to our services. Yet, these instances will be rare in number. 

Zoomonga displays targeted advertisements based on personal information that is exhibited in people's profiles. When you register with us, your personal information and other data will be stored and processed in United States and this information may be subject to the laws of USA jurisidictions. 

To protect your personal information and prevent unauthorized access or data inaccuracies, we employ appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguards to secure the information we collect online. Any sensitive information you enter (such as a credit card number) is encrypted and is protected with state-of-the-art encryption technology. 

We also do everything in our power to protect your information from being disclosed to third parties in violation of our privacy policy. For one, your information is only accessible by those employees who have a need to know the information to perform a specific task. Second, all employees are trained to honor our security and privacy practices. 

To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps through means such as passwords to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections. You can access any information in your posting by going to the area of the site where you submitted the information, and follow the instructions to view, change or delete the information. Nevertheless, please note that deleted or modified information may continue to be stored by Zoomonga for archival record-keeping purposes only. 

By using our website, you consent to the collection and use of this information by Zoomonga. Zoomonga may update this Privacy policy at any time for any reason. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post the new Privacy Policy on this page so that our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. If at any point we decide to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will notify users by way of an email. You will have a choice as to whether we use your information in this different manner. 

Should you have other questions or concerns about this Privacy Policy, please send an email to contact@zoomonga.com.
